Utt Assoratgoon

85 Pattanakarn Rd, Saun Lung, Bangkok TH, 10250 085-834-4114 uttasso@gmail.com

A recent computer engineering graduate with second class honors degree from King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Lardkrabang with experience in programming, data analysis, data visualization, and big data technologies. And also, passionate about learning new development in data analysis and modeling.

EXPERIENCES

Data Engineer at SCB (Siam Commercial Bank)

(June 2019 - Present)

Responsibilities

- Design, Develop and implement data solutions from traditional and nontraditional sources in alignment with project schedule
- Enhance data platform to support robust, scalable and easily accessible application for data analytics
- Build automated processes to support data availability and integration processes
- · Research opportunities for data acquisition and new uses for existing data

Analyzing public transportation GPS Data

Data Analytic project

(Jan 2019 - June 2019)

• Processing GPS data from over 20 GB of every public transportation in Thailand

Software Engineering Internship

Reuter Software (Thailand)

(June 2018 - Dec 2018)

- Gathering system test results and log files which generated by test associated components.
- Implementing database using Elasticsearch to store everyday test results and log files.
- Analyzing the data which stored in Elasticsearch in order to find the outliers in those data.

Capstone Project: Leaf Classification

Data Analytic Course in University

(May 2018)

- Processing data from 1,584 images of leaf specimens (16 samples each of 99 species)
- · Applied machine learning to classify species of the leaf

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming

- Python (Advance)
- Java (Intermediate)
- · C (Intermediate)
- SQL (Intermediate)

Database

- · Elasticsearch(Intermediate)
- MongoDB (Intermediate)
- MySQL (Novice)
- Oracle Database (Novice)

Technology

- Microsoft Azure
- Hadoop
- Hive
- Apache Spark
- CI/CD

Skills

- · Data analytics
- · Machine Learning
- Object-oriented programming

ONLINE COURSE

IBM Data Science

https://www.coursera.org/

Machine Learning A-Z

https://www.superdatascience.com/

Complete Python Bootcamp

https://www.udemy.com/

EDUCATION

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang

Bachelor of engineering in Computer Engineering

GPA: 3.40 / 4.00

Patumwan Demonstration School Srinakarinwirot University

Math and Science (2009-2014)

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership Assign suitable tasks to each team member. Plan and estimate tasks in work cycles, and manage time for each task to ensure the project is completed and delivered on time.
- · Good team player with excellent interaction
- Fast learner Deliver assignments ahead of deadlines without supervisions or classroom courses.
- Punctual: Never late for meetings or classes.
- Cope with unexpected problems using version control (Git) to avoid the risk of losing codes.
- Able to apply Agile Methodology to a project with several requirement changes to optimize quality of the project and to get the best results.